[{"ID":"A2","Question":"You are 27 years old and a single parent of a 3-year-old child. Every Monday through Friday you drive to work, at a restaurant where you earn $7.25/hour. You are only able to work from 11am-5pm because the restaurant does not open until 11am and you need to pick up your child from daycare by 5:30pm. Working 30 hours/week, your monthly gross income is $941.78.\nYour total monthly expenses are $900:\n$600 for rent\n$200 for childcare\n$100 for groceries\n\n(2) On your way to work, you get pulled over for a broken brake light in violation of Wis. Stat. § 347.14. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $150 ticket this month but postpone fixing your brake light.","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and try to get rid of the ticket.","Ignore the brake light ticket for now, hopefully you can pay it off later."],"Navigate":["A6","A9","A12"]},{"ID":"A6","Question":"You paid off your ticket, that means that your monthly expenses were $1,050 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $150 for your brake light ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do? [Q2]","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $450 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but just some of your childcare, you can only afford to pay $50 of your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A16","A20"]},{"ID":"A9","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge agreed to stay the brake light ticket and dismiss it if you show proof that you repaired your brake light within 30 days. Because you missed work, your monthly income is only $898.28. You call some mechanics and the cheapest you can get your brake light fixed is $45. The mechanic is not open on the weekend, and you’ll miss half your shift (3 hours) to get your brake light fixed. What do you do?","Answers":["Don’t fix your brake light, you can’t afford to keep missing work, and don’t pay the ticket. Your monthly income was $898.28. You borrow a bit of money and pay all of your $900 monthly expenses.","Schedule a mechanic and miss half your shift. You spent $45 on this service, but now your brake light ticket will be dismissed."],"Navigate":["A24","A28"]},{"ID":"A12","Question":"You have not paid off your brake light ticket, but you paid all your normal monthly expenses. But you get pulled over again for speeding in violation of Wis. Stat. § 346.57(2). You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $200 under Wis. Stat. § 346.60(3). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $200 speeding ticket this month.","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and contest the speeding ticket.","Ignore the ticket, hopefully you can pay it off later."],"Navigate":["A31","A34","A37"]},{"ID":"A16","Question":"You get pulled over again for speeding in violation of Wis. Stat. § 346.57(2). You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $200 under Wis. Stat. § 346.60(3). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $200 ticket this month.","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and contest the speeding ticket.","Ignore the speeding ticket, hopefully you can pay it off later."],"Navigate":["A40","A43","A46"]},{"ID":"A20","Question":"You get pulled over again for speeding in violation of Wis. Stat. § 346.57(2). You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $200 under Wis. Stat. § 346.60(3).","Answers":["Pay off the $200 speeding ticket this month","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and contest the ticket.","Ignore the speeding ticket, hopefully you can pay it off later."],"Navigate":["A49","A52","A55"]},{"ID":"A24","Question":"You get pulled over again for speeding in violation of Wis. Stat. § 346.57(2). You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $200 under Wis. Stat. § 346.60(3). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $200 speeding ticket this month.","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and contest the ticket.","Ignore the speeding ticket, hopefully you can pay it off later."],"Navigate":["A59","A62","A65"]},{"ID":"A28","Question":"After missing work for court, missing work for the mechanic, and paying the mechanic, you only took home $831.53 this month. You are short on your $900 monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $500 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but just some of your childcare, you can afford to pay $100 of your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A68","A71"]},{"ID":"A31","Question":"You paid off your ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A75","A77"]},{"ID":"A34","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge gave you a point reduction but did not reduce your forfeiture amount. Because you missed a day of work, your monthly income is only $898.28. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay the speeding ticket, making you short for your other monthly expenses","Ignore the ticket and pay your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["A79","A82"]},{"ID":"A37","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for the broken brake light and another for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A85","A87"]},{"ID":"A40","Question":"You paid off your ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A89","A91"]},{"ID":"A43","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge gave you a point reduction but did not reduce your forfeiture amount. Because you missed a day of work, your monthly income is only $898.28. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay the speeding ticket, making you short for your other monthly expenses.","Ignore the speeding ticket and pay your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["A93","A96"]},{"ID":"A46","Question":"You have an unpaid forfeiture for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A99","A101"]},{"ID":"A49","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A103","A105"]},{"ID":"A52","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge gave you a point reduction but did not reduce your forfeiture amount. Because you missed a day of work, your monthly income is only $898.28. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay the speeding ticket, making you short for your other monthly expenses.","Ignore the speeding ticket and pay your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["A107","A110"]},{"ID":"A55","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken in violation of Wis. Stat. § 347.14. You are issued another traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $150 ticket this month but continue to postpone fixing your brake light.","Fix your brake light for $45, missing half your shift at work, but ignore the brake light ticket for now.","Ignore the ticket for now, hopefully you can pay it off later, and postpone fixing your brake light."],"Navigate":["A113","A116","A118"]},{"ID":"A59","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, that means that your monthly expenses were $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A120","A122"]},{"ID":"A62","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge gave you a point reduction but did not reduce your forfeiture amount. Because you missed a day of work, your monthly income is only $898.28. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay the speeding ticket, making you short for your other monthly expenses.","Ignore the speeding ticket and pay your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["A124","A127"]},{"ID":"A65","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for the broken brake light and another for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A130","A132"]},{"ID":"A68","Question":"You get pulled over again for speeding in violation of Wis. Stat. § 346.57(2). You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $200 under Wis. Stat. § 346.60(3). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $200 speeding ticket this month.","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and contest the speeding ticket."],"Navigate":["A134","A137"]},{"ID":"A71","Question":"You get pulled over again for speeding in violation of Wis. Stat. § 346.57(2). You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $200 under Wis. Stat. § 346.60(3). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the $200 speeding ticket this month.","Miss a day of work to go to court, without a lawyer, and contest the speeding ticket.","Ignore the ticket, hopefully you can pay it off later."],"Navigate":["A140","A143","A146"]},{"ID":"A75","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the speeding ticket, making you short on your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A77","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Pay off the ticket, making you short on your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A79","Question":"You paid off your ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A149","A151"]},{"ID":"A82","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for the broken brake light and another for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A153","A155"]},{"ID":"A85","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A87","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you keep paying rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A89","Question":"You have now paid only a portion of your rent two months in a row ($450/$600 last month and $400/$600 thidids month). Your landlord gives you an eviction notice. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you are evicted, you will not be able to find another apartment."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A91","Question":"Your childcare provider warns you that you need to makeup this month’s payment within two weeks or you can no longer bring your child. You have no way to catch up, and so you quit your job and stay home with your child. Now your income is gone. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you cannot pay your rent, you risk eviction."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A93","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $390 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A157","A159"]},{"ID":"A96","Question":"You have an unpaid forfeiture for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A161","A163"]},{"ID":"A99","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A101","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you don’t pay rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work. "],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A103","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to pay all these forfeitures."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A105","Question":"This is the second month in a row that you have missed parts of your childcare payment (last month you paid $50/$200, this month you paid $0/$200). Your childcare provider tells you to stop bringing your child until you make up the full $350 you owe. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. Without childcare, you cannot work. You need income."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A107","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A165","A167"]},{"ID":"A110","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for the broken brake light and another for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?(instead says 1 unpaid, driver’s license suspended)","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A169","A171"]},{"ID":"A113","Question":"By paying the ticket, you will be short on your normal monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $450 of your $600 rent. (instead gives eviction warning)","Pay your normal expenses but just some of your childcare, you can only afford to pay $50 of your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A173","A175"]},{"ID":"A116","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for speeding and another for the second broken brake light violation. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your broken brake light conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need your license back to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A118","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for speeding and another for the second broken brake light violation. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your broken brake light conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need your license back to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A120","Question":"Your landlord warns you that if you miss rent again, he’ll serve an eviction notice. What do you do?(instead, says you get pulled over again for brake light)","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to catch up on rent, and you can’t risk being evicted."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A122","Question":"Your childcare provider warns you that you need to make up this month’s payment within two weeks or you can no longer bring your child. You have no way to catch up, and so you quit your job and stay home with your child. Now your income is gone. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you cannot pay your rent, you risk eviction."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A124","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, that means that your monthly expenses were $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent. (instead, says you get pulled over again for brake light)","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A177","A179"]},{"ID":"A127","Question":"You have two unpaid forfeitures, one for the broken brake light and another for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A181","A183"]},{"ID":"A130","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A132","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you keep paying rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A134","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A185","A187"]},{"ID":"A137","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge gave you a point reduction but did not reduce your forfeiture amount. Because you missed a day of work, your monthly income is only $898.28. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay the speeding ticket, making you short for your other monthly expenses.","Ignore the speeding ticket and pay your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["A189","A191"]},{"ID":"A140","Question":"You paid off your speeding ticket, making your monthly expenses $1,100 (your normal monthly expenses of $900 + $200 for your speeding ticket). This means that you were short on your monthly expenses. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay your normal expenses but just some of your rent, you can only afford to pay $400 of your $600 rent.","Pay your normal expenses but you cannot afford to pay your $200 childcare."],"Navigate":["A193","A195"]},{"ID":"A143","Question":"You missed a day of work and went to court without a lawyer. The judge gave you a point reduction but did not reduce your forfeiture amount. Because you missed a day of work, your monthly income is only $898.28. What do you do?","Answers":["Pay the speeding ticket, making you short for your other monthly expenses.","Ignore the speeding ticket and pay your normal monthly expenses."],"Navigate":["A197","A199"]},{"ID":"A146","Question":"You have an unpaid forfeiture, for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Keep driving and ignore the suspension.","Stop driving until you can get your license back."],"Navigate":["A201","A203"]},{"ID":"A149","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to pay all these forfeitures."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A151","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to pay all these forfeitures."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A153","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A155","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you keep paying rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A157","Question":"You have now paid only a portion of your rent two months in a row ($450/$600 last month and $390/$600 this month). Your landlord gives you an eviction notice. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you are evicted, you will not be able to find another apartment."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A159","Question":"Your childcare provider warns you that you need to make up this month’s payment within two weeks or you can no longer bring your child. You have no way to catch up, and so you quit your job and stay home with your child. Now your income is gone. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you cannot pay your rent, you risk eviction."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A161","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A163","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you keep paying rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A165","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You are issued a traffic citation with a forfeiture of $150 under Wis. Stat. § 347.30(2). What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to pay all these forfeitures."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A167","Question":"This is the second month in a row that you have missed parts of your childcare payment (last month you paid $50/$200, this month you paid $0/$200). Your childcare provider tells you to stop bringing your child until you make up the full $350 you owe. What do you do?\t","Answers":["Seek help. Without childcare, you cannot work. You need income."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A169","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A171","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you can’t pay rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A173","Question":"Your landlord warns you that if you miss rent again, he’ll serve an eviction notice. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to catch up on rent, and you can’t risk being evicted."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A175","Question":"This is the second month in a row that you have missed parts of your childcare payment (last month you paid $50/$200, this month you paid $50/$200). Your childcare provider tells you to stop bringing your child until you make up the full $350 you owe. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. You don’t have a way to pay all these forfeitures."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A177","Question":"Your landlord warns you that if you miss rent again, he’ll serve an eviction notice. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to catch up on rent, and you can’t risk being evicted."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A179","Question":"Your childcare provider warns you that you need to make up this month’s payment within two weeks or you can no longer bring your child. You have no way to catch up, and so you quit your job and stay home with your child. Now your income is gone. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you cannot pay your rent, you risk eviction."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A181","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again because it is still broken. You receive a ticket for the broken brake light and another for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A183","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you keep paying rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A185","Question":"You have now paid only a portion of your rent two months in a row ($500/$600 last month and $400/$600 this month). Your landlord gives you an eviction notice. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you are evicted, you will not be able to find another apartment."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A187","Question":"Your childcare provider warns you that you need to make up this month’s payment within two weeks or you can no longer bring your child. You have no way to catch up, and so you quit your job and stay home with your child. Now your income is gone. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you cannot pay your rent, you risk eviction"],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A189","Question":"You will be short on either rent or childcare for the second time in a row. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. Losing your housing or childcare would be an impossible burden to overcome."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A191","Question":"You have an unpaid forfeiture, for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A193","Question":"Your landlord warns you that if you miss rent again, he’ll serve an eviction notice. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. You don’t know how to catch up on rent, and you can’t risk being evicted."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A195","Question":"This is the second month in a row that you have missed parts of your childcare payment (last month you paid $100/$200, this month you paid $0/$200). Your childcare provider tells you to stop bringing your child until you make up the full $350 you owe. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. If you cannot pay your rent, you risk eviction."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A197","Question":"You will be short on either rent or childcare for the second time in a row. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek help. Losing your housing or childcare would be an impossible burden to overcome."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A199","Question":"You have an unpaid forfeiture, for speeding. Your driver’s license is suspended for one year from the date of your speeding conviction. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A201","Question":"The same police officer who pulled you over for a broken brake light pulls you over again. You receive a ticket for driving without a license under Wis. Stat. § 343.05(3)(a) with a forfeiture of $300. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]},{"ID":"A203","Question":"Without driving, you cannot get to work, and you are worried you’ll be evicted if you keep paying rent. What do you do?","Answers":["Seek legal help. The forfeitures are becoming insurmountable, and you need to drive to work."],"Navigate":["NULL"]}]